eztalks.com 2018-09-07

# Privacy | ezTalks

Last updated: May 25, 2018

This Privacy Policy describes how ezTalks Technology Company Limited (“we”, us”, “our”) collect and use your personal data when you access and use our products and services (collectively “Products”) or visit ezTalks website. This policy covers ezTalks website ([www.eztalks.com](https://www.eztalks.com/)), mobile applications, and desktop clients and is applicable worldwide. For privacy practices when customers use our application and cloud-based services, please refer to ezTalks's Service Privacy Policy eztalks.com/service-privacy.

This policy outlines our handling practices, how we collect and use the personal information you provide through online and offline. It also describes the choices available to you regarding the use of, your access to, and how to update and correct your personal information. By providing us with your personal data when using the Service, you consent to the processing of your personal data as described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not access or use the Service. This policy may be updated from time to time and ezTalks Service will indicate when the policy has been updated. 

### Collection of your personal information

We collect information from you when you voluntarily provide that information to us. "Personal Information" is any information that can be used to identify an individual, and may include, but is not limited to, name, email address, postal or other physical address, credit or debit card number, title, information generated from use of our Products, and other information required to provide a Product, deliver a product, or carry out a transaction you have requested. Your Personal Information may be collected in the below described situations:

  * • registration
  * • use of certain Product features
  * • billing and collecting payments for our Products
  * • placing transactions or orders
  * • registering for membership programs or newsletter subscriptions
  * • requesting service and support for our Products and providing such support
  * • generating reports based on information collected from use of our Products
  * • customizing the advertising and content you see
  * • registering to attend a seminar or webinar
  * • participating in an online survey
  * • submitting an entry for an opt-in sweepstakes or other promotion
  * • participating in discussion groups or forums

### Uses of your Personal Information

How we use the information is shaped by the source of the information, the type of Products you choose, and any privacy preferences that you have specified to us. Some of the ways we may use your Personal Information include:

  * • To process your orders and deliver the products and Products that you have ordered.
  * • To provide reports based on information collected from use of our Products.
  * • To provide information on your request to another individual such as a friend or co-worker.
  * • To provide the ability to contact you, and provide you with shipping and billing information.
  * • To conduct questionnaires and surveys in order to provide better products and services to our customers and end users. Your completion of any questionnaires is voluntary.
  * • To provide customer feedback and support.
  * • To provide support and assistance for our products and Products.
  * • To provide opt-in contests, sweepstakes or other marketing or promotional activities on the ezTalks website. Personal Information may be collected to administer those programs.
  * • To support recruitment inquiries.
  * • To understand more about you, so we can personalize newsletters and websites to your preferences. For example, allow you the opportunity to request specific information on products and services that may be of interest.
  * • To meet contract obligations.
  * • To provide the ability to create personal profile areas and view protected content.
  * • To keep you up to date on the latest Product announcements, software updates, software upgrades, system enhancements, special offers, and other information, provided that you can edit your marketing preferences at any time as described below.

### Referrals

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our website, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the website. ezTalks may stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. Your friend may contact us at [support@eztalks.com](mailto:support@eztalks.com) to request that we remove this information from our database.

### Accessing and updating your Personal Information

ezTalks may obtain some Personal Information regarding you from Facebook. In order to keep your Personal Information accurate and up to date or to delete any Personal Information, you will need to manage that through your Facebook account. We do not have the ability to modify or delete your Facebook Personal Information. Upon request ezTalks will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your personal information. You may access, correct, or request deletion of your personal information by sending an email request to [support@eztalks.com](mailto:support@eztalks.com). We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe. We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

### Unsubscribing and Opting Out

Each promotional email from ezTalks or from third parties to whom ezTalks has given your email address with your consent includes instructions on how you can unsubscribe from that category of mailing or from receiving email from that third party.

You may also unsubscribe from ezTalks's promotional emails by sending an email, including your name and email address to [support@eztalks.com](mailto:support@eztalks.com).

If you have additional questions regarding your disclosure choices and ezTalks's policies regarding receipt of promotional email, you may contact ezTalks by sending an email with your name and email address to [admin@eztalks.com](mailto:admin@eztalks.com).

### Passive Collection

We gather certain information automatically. This information may include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, the files viewed on our site (e.g., HTML pages, graphics, etc.), operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data to analyze trends in the aggregate and administer the site.

In addition, by using some of our Products, network information may be transmitted back to us such as Product usage information. This information is transmitted back to us so we can determine how users are interacting with our Products, to assist us with improving our Products, and to correct any problems that may occur.

### Cookies and Tracking Technologies

ezTalks and our partners use cookies or similar technologies to track user traffic patterns and hold certain registration information and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. While we maintain ownership of this data, we do not share this type of data about individual users with third parties.Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level.

### Mobile Application

When you download and use our Services, we automatically collect information on the type of device you use, operating system version, and the device identifier (or "UDID").

We send you push notifications from time-to-time in order to update you about any events or promotions that we may be running. If you no longer wish to receive these types of communications, you may turn them off at the device level. To ensure you receive proper notifications, we will need to collect certain information about your device such as operating system and user identification information.

### Geolocation

We may utilize your location based information precise to optimizing your connection to our data center and we will share this information with our data center provider for the sole purpose of providing you this service. 

If you do not wish to allow us to share your information in this manner please opt-out by contacting us at [support@eztalks.com](mailto:support@eztalks.com). You may opt-out of location based services at any time by editing the setting at the device level or by emailing us at [support@eztalks.com](mailto:support@eztalks.com). 

### Sharing your personal information

ezTalks will ensure your privacy and we do not sell or share your personal information with third parties except granted by you or as described in this privacy policy. We may share information with a strict need-to-know under appropriate confidentiality obligations which may include:

  * • We may share your Personal Information within ezTalks and its affiliated companies and with third party service providers for purposes of data processing or storage.
  * • We may also share your Personal Information with business partners, service vendors, authorized third-party agents or contractors in order to provide a requested Product or transaction, including processing orders, processing credit card transactions, hosting websites, hosting event and seminar registration and providing customer support.
  * • We may respond to subpoenas, court orders, or similar legal process by disclosing your Personal Information and other related information, if necessary; We also may choose to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.
  * • We may collect and possibly share Personal Information and any other additional information available to us in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of ezTalks’s terms of service, or as otherwise required by law.
  * • We only provide these third parties with the minimum amount of Personal Information necessary to complete/utilize the requested Product or transaction, and the third parties are not permitted to use your Personal Information except for limited purpose of completing/providing the requested Product or transaction.
  * • We will ask for your consent before we use or share your information for any purpose other than the reason you provided it or as otherwise provided by this policy. In order to let us know your preferences, we will require an action on your part, such as checking the appropriate option, to indicate your consent.

We will ask for your consent before we use or share your information for any purpose other than the reason you provided it or as otherwise provided by this policy. In order to let us know your preferences, we will require an action on your part, such as checking the appropriate option, to indicate your consent.

While navigating ezTalks's web site or Products you may be directed to content or functionality that is hosted by a third-party supplier. When information is collected on behalf of ezTalks exclusively, ezTalks's privacy policy will be referenced and will govern how your information is used. For other, non-ezTalks sites or services, the site/service owner's privacy policy will be referenced. You should review such supplier's privacy and security policies prior to use.

### Security of your Personal Information

We take reasonable steps to protect the Personal Information from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, and destruction. We utilize a combination of industry-standard security technologies, procedures, and organizational measures to help protect your information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure.

When we transfer credit card information over the Internet, we protect it using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption technology.

No Internet, e-mail or other electronic transmission is ever fully secure or error free, We recommend you to take every precaution in protecting your Personal Information when you are on the Internet. For example, change your passwords often, use a combination of letters and numbers when creating passwords, and make sure you use a secure browser.

If you have any questions about the security of your personal information, you can contact us at [support@eztalks.com](mailto:support@eztalks.com). 

### Linked websites and third party services

Our websites and services may provide links to other third-party websites and services which are outside our control and not covered by this policy. We encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on these (and all) sites you visit or services you use.

### Newsgroups/forums

If you participate in an ezTalks discussion forum or chat room, you should be aware that the information you provide there will be made broadly available to others, potentially inside or outside ezTalks, who have access to that discussion forum or chat room. Also, please recognize that individual forums and chat rooms may have additional rules and conditions. Each participant's opinion on a forum or chat room is his or her own and should not be considered as reflecting the opinion of ezTalks.

### Consent to Transfer, Processing and Storage of Personal Information

We may transfer your Personal Information to any ezTalks affiliate worldwide, or to third parties acting on our behalf for the purposes of processing or storage, and by providing any Personal Information you fully understand and unambiguously consent to such transfer, processing and storage of such information.

### EU-U.S. Privacy Shield and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Statement

ezTalks participates in and has certified its compliance with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield. ezTalks is committed to subjecting all personal data received from European Union (EU) member countries and Switzerland, in reliance on the Privacy Shield Framework, to the Framework's applicable Principles. 

ezTalks is responsible for the processing of personal data it receives, under the Privacy Shield Framework, and subsequently transfers to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf. ezTalks complies with the Privacy Shield Principles for all onward transfers of personal data from the EU and Switzerland, including the onward transfer liability provisions.

With respect to personal data received or transferred pursuant to the Privacy Shield Frameworks, ezTalks is subject to the regulatory enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission. In certain situations, ezTalks may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

### Policy updates

ezTalks may amend this privacy statement from time to time, and at any time. We will post a notice on this website whenever this privacy statement is materially changed. Your continued use of the ezTalks website or Products after any change will signify and confirm your assent to those changes.
